The salience model, we're
still identifying stakeholders
and this is one of the
ways to categorize them.
So salience model isn't a grid.
That's why you see three circles.
So we are now looking at the stakeholders
based on their power, their urgency,
need for information, need for attention,
and legitimacy.
Is there a involvement in our project
appropriate.
All right.
So anywhere you start to see these circles
intertwine.
These are your key stakeholders,
especially seven.
They have power.
They have a high level
of need for attention,
And their involvement
is definitely legitimate.
And then anywhere else, you can have you
could end up with more stakeholders in
each of these areas of course wherever
they intersect these are your key
stakeholders so they just they have a
legend over here on the right one is
dormant two discretionary three demanding
four dominant five dangerous six dependent
seven definitive and eight is a non-state
I don't think you have to memorize those.
Just be familiar with our three
points, power, urgency, legitimacy,
and where they intersect,
those are our key stakeholders.